（男鹿）いででで…。
Oww!
（ラミア）
ちょっと　動くんじゃないわよ！
ぐぐっ…がっ！
Hey, don't move!
（ラミア）
あんたの手当てしてやってる
だけでも　ありがたく思いなさい！
You should be thankful
I'm treating you at all!
…てか　首！
しっかり　首しまってる。
My neck! You're choking me!
（ベル坊）アウアウ…。
（ラミア）
まったく…アランドロンに
言われるままに来てみたら→
Jeez! I came after Alaindelon told me.
ヒルダ姉さま
めちゃくちゃ重傷じゃない！→
And just look at how bad Hilda's
injury is, you good-for-nothing!
この甲斐性なし！
ぐわ～うう…。
（邦枝）あの…あと
私がやっとこうか？
Um, maybe I should take over?
ハァ！？誰あんた？
引っ込んでなさいよ　ブス！
Huh? Who are you?
ううっ…。
Get the hell out, Ugly!
いやいや　私のせいで　こうなった
みたいなとこあるから…ね？
Now, now...
It's also somewhat my fault
that this happened, so...
だから　誰よ！
あなたこそ何！？
Okay?
Yeah, and you are...?
悪魔？
どうせ　悪魔なんでしょ！？
I should ask you the same thing!
A Demon? Some Demon, right?
ちょっと　手はなしなさいよ！
首…首が…。
Let go, you!
ダァ～！
M-My neck!
（騒ぎ声）
（早乙女）やれやれ…。→
お騒がせして　すみませんな～。→
Sheesh...
Sorry for all the ruckus.
あっ　すぐ帰りますんで
おかまいなく。
We'll be heading back soon. Thank you.
ダブダブ…ダァダァ～ダァ～。（２人）んっ？
（早乙女）んっ？
（ラミア・邦枝）あっ！？
（邦枝）あっ！
（ラミア）師匠！
（フォルカス）フ～…やれやれ。
Doctor!
師匠！
ぐっ！ふがっ！？
Honestly...
Doctor!
（邦枝）
ヒルダさんは大丈夫なんですか？
ヒルダ姉さまは！？
（ラミア）
Is Hilda-san okay?
How is Miss Hilda?
それなんだが…。
Well, about that...
（２人）あっ…。
ダッ？
It's Time for Training
（フォルカス）ヒルダの容体だが→
Hilda's condition is far from good, but
I do not feel it is life threatening.
あまり良い状態とは言えんが
命に別状はないだろう。→
あと少し遅ければ
危なかったがな…。
Still, even a little later,
and we might have lost her.
ハァ…。
（２人）
（フォルカス）そこのお嬢さんの的確な
応急処置のおかげだな。
It's thanks to the first-aid
of this lady here.
えっ…。
ムッ！
よかった…。
つ～か…おまえ慣れすぎ。
Thank goodness.
So you're just accepting all this?
だって　ヒルダさんは私を助けて
あんな大ケガしたんでしょ！→
But Hilda-san got injured
because she was saving me!
それなのに悪魔が　どうとか→
And besides, I can't go getting
shocked each time I see a Demon...
いちいち驚いてる場合じゃ
ないじゃない。
（早乙女）な～　邦枝。
んっ？
（２人）
So Kunieda, I understand how
you feel, but it's gotten late.
おまえの気持ちも　わかるがな
今日は　もう遅い。→
侍女悪魔ちゃんの容体も
わかったんだ。→
You know the prognosis
of the Demon Maidservant,
そろそろ　おいとまするぞ。
それに…。
so it's about time to leave.
And besides...
ぐっ！
元はといえば
こいつが弱いせいだしな。→
Basically it's all because
this guy's weak.
ハッハハハ…。
おいこら　明日も学校　来いよ。→
Hey, you. Get your butt to school tomorrow.
ちゃんと
力の使い方　教えてやっからな。
I'll teach you the right
way to use that power!
くっ…。
（フォルカス）((困りますな　早乙女殿→
This is a problem, Saotome-dono.
あまり
ベルゼ様１人に肩入れされては))
If you support Beelze-sama
too much on your own...
((ああ　わかってるよ。
クソったれ))
Yeah, I know, you piece of crap.
《校長の　じじいに頼まれたんだ…
しょ～がね～だろ…》
The Principal asked me. I had to do it.
（美咲）あら　もう帰んの？
はい　お邪魔しました。
Oh, heading home already?
Yes. Sorry to bother you.
残念ね～　泊まってけば？
What a shame. What if you stay the night?
えっ！？いえ　そんな…。
Oh, I couldn't...
ねえ　あなた烈怒帝瑠の総長
なんだって？
えっ！？
You're the head of the Red Tails, I hear?
Oh, but... That's all in the past.
いや　あの
それは昔の話でして…。
ふ～ん。ま…いいから　いいから
なっつかしいわね～。またおいで！
Ah, don't worry about it...
Man, brings back memories!
Come back any time!
（アランドロン）
ニョロっとね。
突然ですが　男鹿殿の姉上の→
*squirm*
Sorry for the interruption,
but Oga's older sister, Misaki-sama, seems
to be a former leader of the Red Tails.
美咲様は烈怒帝瑠の初代総長だったそうですぞ。ニュルっとな。
*wiggle*
辰巳～！この子
ちゃんと送って行きなさいよ～。
Tatsumi! You take her home right, now!
うっせ～な～。
着替えぐらいさせろよ。→
Oh, shut up!
At least let me change clothes.
ハァ…ったく
今日は　なんつ～日だ…。
Man, what a day.
プゥ～…。ニョ？
（ヒルダ）何をガン見しておる。
What are you staring at?
うっわ～　起きてたのかよ！？
ダ～ッ！！
You're awake?
フン！貴様のベッドでは
臭くて眠れんわ。
Your bed stinks. It's
keeping me from sleeping.
ほ～　元気そうでなによりだな。
Oh? Glad to see you're still kickin'.
あの男は帰ったのか？
Did that man leave?
ん？ああ　あのバンダナ野郎か…
ついさっきな。
Oh, the guy with the bandana?
Yeah, a little while ago.
（ヒルダ）そうか…。なぁ…。
あ？
I see.
Hey.
すまなかったな…。
I'm sorry.
ん？…今なんて？
（ヒルダ）２度は言わん。
What did you...?
I won't say it again.
私の方が
足を引っぱってしまった→
It was I who held you back.
あの状況で　坊っちゃまが→
無傷だったのは奇跡に近い…
It's nearly a miracle that the
Master escaped unharmed from that.
情けない話だがな…。
ダブ～…。
Though it pains me to say it.
いや　もっと他に
言うべき事があるはずだが…→
Well, there is more I should say...
うまく言葉が出んな…
疲れた…少し寝る。
But the words aren't coming to me.
I'm tired. I'll rest a while.
くそぉ～～！
ムカつくぅ～～！
Damn it!
Pisses me off!
ごめんね　降りようか？
あ！？んなこっちゃね～よ！
I'm sorry! Should I get off?
Not you!
バブバフ　バフブ～。
どいつもこいつも　知った風な顔で
勝手なことばかり言いやがる！
Each and every one of 'em doin'
whatever the hell they want!
They think they know everything!
冗談じゃねぇ！こっちは
巻き込まれっぱなしだぞ！？
Give me a break!
I'm caught up in one thing and then another!
うん…。
ダ～ダブ　ダ～ダブダ～。
その子も　本当に
拾った子だったのね。
You really just picked the little guy up?
ああ　そうだよ！
偶然　川で拾ったんだ！→
Yeah, that's right.
I picked him up by the river.
偶然　川で拾って　なつかれて
そしたら魔王で→
I picked him up, he took a liking to me,
and then Hilda came to my place talkin' about
人間滅ぼすだの何だのと
ヒルダが　うちに居ついて…。
wiping out humanity and
Demon Lords or whatever!
ダビ～　ダビ～！！
あげくのはてに　こいつのアニキの
部下が　オレを殺しに来ただぁ！？
And to top it off, his older brother's
minions are coming to kill me?!
マジ意味わかんねぇよ！→
I don't get this one bit!
…とか思ってたのによ。
...is how I thought.
何でかな…。
あっ…。
But... what really pisses me off now
is that I couldn't protect everyone.
今は…
守りきれなかった事がムカつく。
てめえの弱さも！
ヒルダの　しおらしさも！
Your weakness, Hilda being meek...
あのエラ野郎の　したり顔も！
That bigshot lookin' like he's all that...
早乙女とかいう
ヒゲバンダナの先公ヅラも！
And that bearded bandana guy, Saotome,
thinkin' he's some kind of teacher...
全部　ムカつく！
They all piss me off!
うん…。
強くならなきゃなんねぇ…
全員まとめて黙らせるくらいに。
I've gotta get stronger...
Strong enough to shut them all up!
ダブダブ～！！
おおっ！
おまえも　そう思うか　ベル坊！
You think so too, Baby Beel?
もっと　雄叫ベ！
ダブダ　ブェブェ～！！
Scream louder!
ちょっと近所迷惑でしょ！うぉ～～！！
Hey! You're going to
disturb the neighborhood!
うぉ～～！！ダァ～！！
（邦枝）うわっ！静かにしなさ～い！
Quiet down!
（邦枝）それで　どうするの？
あ？
So what are you going to do?
（邦枝）強くなるって　やっぱり
早乙女先生の所に行くの？
Get stronger? Then you're going
to Saotome-sensei's place?
それは…いや！
ニョ！
That one's a...
...no.
男には　ゆずれない
プライドというもんがある。
ダーダー！
There's a certain pride
that men cannot ignore.
あ～　そういうもんなの？
（邦枝の祖父）こら！葵！
Oh, I suppose...
Hey, Aoi!
ん！
（祖父）こんの不良娘が！→
You trouble-making girl!
こんな夜遅くまで
フラフラしおって！
What are you doing wandering
around so late at night?
いや　これはね…。
あっ！
ニョ！
Oh, you see...
むっ！？
おぬし　いつぞやの見所のある
悪タレか？何しに来た？
I've seen you before, you mischievous scamp.
What have you come here for?
何しにって…。
What for?
《まてよ？
あのヒゲバンダナじゃなくて→
Wait...
If I train at this old man's place
instead of Mr. Beard Bandanna...
この
じじいのとこで修行すれば…》
（早乙女）やあ！男鹿きゅん！→
Hey there, Oga-kyun!
今日は先生が技とか
教えてあげるよ！
I'm gonna teach you a special move today!
うるさいぞ～　ヒゲポン。→
Shut up, Beard-brain!
ボクは　君の教えなんて
必要ないんだよ。
I don't need to get taught by you!
くらえ！はぁぁ～～！！
Take this!
百鼻乱桜拳！
うわ～！！
（早乙女）
Countless Petals Scattering
Sakura Blossom Fist!
（早乙女）強い～。まいりました。
So strong!
I lose.
わかれば　よろしい。
As long as you understand!
あ～…フッ。
きまってんじゃね～か。
（２人）ん？
Why else?
修行とやらを…受けに来たぜ。
I've come here...
...to receive your training.
ほう…。
えっ？ちょっと男鹿！？
それは…。
Wait, Oga... That's...
ほほう！
えっ！
フッフフフ…。
（祖父）フッフフフ…。
ダッブ…ブフフッ…。
フッフフフ…。
（祖父）
ダブフフッ…。
フッフフフ…。
んっ…。
（姫川）東条と出馬がケンカ？
Tojo and Izuma were fighting?
（由加）そ～なんスよ！しかも
他校の不良が乱入して→
Yeah, and like some punks from another
school showed up, and everyone was in big trouble...
大ピンチのとこを
かけつけた神崎さんが→
Kanzaki came runnin' and
finished 'em all off!
キッチリ
おさめてくれちゃって～！
（由加）マジパネっスよ～！
見せたかったっスね～！
It was crazy, man! You shoulda seen it.
（姫川）ほ～。
あっ　信じてないっしょ？
You don't believe me, do ya?
いえいえ…。
Oh, sure...
（神崎）
フッ…よせよ。花澤。
あんまり言うとカッコ悪いだろ？
Enough with that Hanazawa.
It's not cool to talk about it too much.
真の　つわものは寡黙なもんさ。
The truly strong need few words.
（由加）うわ～　カッケ～！
バカッケ～！！→
Whoa! So cool! Awesome!
うわぁ～～！！
（姫川）どこがだよ。
As if.
（古市）
確かに　東条先輩　休みっスね。
（千秋）うん　うん。
Tojo-senpai actually is absent, though.
（寧々）まあ…アイツは　いつもの事だから　いいとして→
Well, that's usual for him.
葵姐さんまで休みって
どういうこと？
But Madame Aoi absent as well?
What's going on?
男鹿もですよ…あの２人
この前　一緒に帰ってましたけど。
So is Oga.
The two of them went home
together before, so...
そう…あっ！
Yeah...
あっ！
（古市・寧々）まさか！？
（千秋）んっ…。
It couldn't be!
フッフフフ…。
It's finally time.
いよいよだな。
ダブッ！
Just you watch me, Beard-bandanna!
見てろよ　ヒゲバンダナ！
オレは新しく生まれかわる！
I'm going to be born anew!
ここから　ニューオレ様が
飛び立つのだ！
ダァ！！
This is the place where the
Great New Me makes his debut!
ハ～ッハハハッ…。
ダァ～ダッダッダッ！
ぐはっ！
（祖父）朝から　うるさい。
Pipe down, it's early.
You actually came here to train?
（邦枝）まさか…
本気で修行に来たの？
なんか　いろいろ間違ってると
思うんだけど…。
I think you must be confused about things...
（祖父）おまえこそ
早く学校に行かんか。
And you, get to school already!
How can I do that?
（邦枝）
そういう訳にも　いかないでしょ！第一　男鹿はいいの！？→
Are you sure about this, Oga?
うちの　おじいちゃんが
修行相手で！
You'll let my grandpa train you?
あ？…おじいちゃん？
Grandpa?
えっ！？
（祖父）どしたの？
What's up?
《しまったぁ～！！
そういえば前に→
Oh, crap!
Now that I think about it, I was in
disguise that time at the mountain shrine!
山寺で会った時は
変装してたんだ～！！》
((そう　くにえ！
青井くにえ　っていうの！))
Right!
Kunie! I'm Aoi Kunie!
《ど…どうしよう～…》
W-What'll I do?
じ～っ…。
ギクッ！
まさか　おまえ…。
（邦枝）ちちち…違うのよ！→
Don't tell me, you're...
N-N-N-N-No, I'm not!
いや　違わないけど！！別に騙すとかそ～いうんじゃなくて！
I mean, I am, but...
I wasn't trying to hide it, or anything...
ん？光太じゃねぇか？
（邦枝）えっ！？
Isn't that Kouta?
（光太）アウアウ…。
《ああ～っ！！
これは決定的～！！》
There's no doubt now!
I knew it.
やっぱりな。
ハッ！？
Kunieda... You're...
邦枝…おまえ…。
《ううっ～…怒ってる～
どうしよう～…嫌われたぁ～》
Oh, no! He's angry!
He's going to hate me now!
...Aoi Kunie's cousin?!
青井くにえの
いとこだったのか～！
はっ？
フッ…アイツには何となく
親近感あってよ→
I could tell somehow you two were related.
お互い　がんばろうぜって言っといてくれや。
Tell her for me to keep up the good fight!
え…あっ…アハハハ！
あったり！→
Spot on! Yup, I'm Kunie's cousin!
そうそう
くにえのイトコなの～　うん！
There I go again...
《またやっちゃった～》
アウ。
Faculty Office
（早乙女）あ～　くそぉ！→
Crap.
勝手に学校休んで
何やってんだ？あのバカ！
What the hell is that idiot
doing skipping school?
Man...
…ったく。（ドアをたたく音）
来たか。あいてるよ。
Is that him?
It's open!
We finally meet again, Saotome Zenjurou.
≪やっと見つけたぜ
早乙女禅十郎≫
Oh? A different idiot showed up.
ほう。別のバカが来たか。
I mean... Zen-san.
（東条）いや…禅さん。
久しぶりだな　虎。
Long time no see, Tora.
たあああ～！
はあああ～！
《こ　これが修業の第一段階か！？→
This is the first step in my training?!
確かにキツイ！キツイぞ！》
It's definitely harsh!
Really harsh!
しか～し！
However!
If I overcome it, I'll be born anew!
これを　のりこえた時こそ
新たに生まれかわった→
ニューオレ様が誕生…→
The Great New Me will make his appearance!
As if!
しね～よ！
This is just a damn dust cloth!
これはただの　ゾーキンがけだろ！？つべこべ言わずにやらんか！
Would you do it without complaining?
まずは己をみがく前に
道場をみがく。基本じゃ基本。
Before you polish yourself,
you must polish the dojo!
The basics, the basics.
Oh, and when that's done,
then you clean the grounds!
ああ　それが終わったら
境内のそうじじゃからな。
くっ…。
だから言ったのに。
See what I mean?
You'd definitely do better learning
from Saotome-sensei than my grandpa.
おじいちゃんに習うより
絶対　早乙女先生のところに→
行った方がいいって。
今からでも頭下げに行きなさいよ。
Just suck it up and ask for his help.
フッ…何言ってんだ　ようやく
わかってきたぜ。アレだろ？
What are you talking about?
I finally understand!
It's that, right?
At a glance the movement seems pointless,
この一見意味のない動きが　実は→
but it'll end up being the basics
of some martial arts move, right?
武術の体さばきに
なってるっつ～か→
One of those, right?
そ～いうヤツだろ？
映画でみたことあんぜ！
I totally saw that in the movies!
だったら！鏡みたいに
ピッカピカにしてやんぜ～！
So...
I'll shine it till I can see my face in it!
いや　ただの日課だってば。
No, it's just a daily chore.
アダダダ…。
うん？あんたも強くなりたいの？
You want to get stronger too?
アイ！アイダダ…。
He does resemble Oga, doesn't he?
（邦枝）《やっぱ男鹿に
似てるわよね。カワイイ》
So cute...
（光太）ひゅい～…。
あっ。ダ？ダダ？
フッ…。
キイイーッ！
ングググ…。
アヤヤヤーッ！
ダダ！？…バァ～！
アウ？
ウ～…ダッ！
あ…。
おい　どうした？大丈夫か？
Hey, what's wrong? You okay?
クッ…ヒィ～…。
えっ！？
ビエ…エ…。
ビエエエ～ッ！
ギャアアア～ッ！
何だ～！？どうしたベル坊～！
What? What's wrong, Baby Beel?!
《カワイイけど
やっぱ悪魔なのよね》
He's cute, but... definitely a Demon.
フッ…。
Yeah, I guess you had it rough too, Tora.
（早乙女）
そうか　お前も災難だったな　虎。
ん～　よくわからんが　禅さんは
昨日のヤツらのこと知ってんのか？
I don't really get it, but you know
this guy from yesterday, Zen-san?
何回同じ説明させる気だよ。→
How many times do I have to explain it?
I'm telling you, he was a real Demon!
だから！そいつらは悪魔で！
Right! He was as strong as a Demon!
おう！悪魔のように強かったぞ。
Not "as strong"! An actual Demon!
じゃなくて悪魔なの！
禅さんの知り合いか？
You know him, Zen-san?
知り合いじゃね～よ！
違うのか？
I don't know him!
You don't?
そこはいいんだよ　ど～でも！
That doesn't matter, okay?!
Don't you understand?
わかってんのか！？お前　一歩
間違えたら　死んでたんだぞ！
One mistake and you'd be dead meat!
そう熱くなるなよ　先生。
オレは自分に何が起きたか→
No need to get so upset, Sensei.
I don't really know what happened to me yet.
まだ　よくわからねえんだ。
もう一度最初から説明してくれ。
Could you explain it to
me again, from the start?
オレ　すげぇ強えヤツと
ケンカしたんだ。
I fought with this crazy strong guy...
でも　メチャクチャに
やられちまってよ。
But I was beat bad... Real bad.
Put ashes in the ashtray! And be quiet!
（早乙女）お前も災難だったな。
（東条）ああ　まるで
悪魔のように強かったな。
I guess you had it rough too.
Yeah, he was as strong as a Demon.
（早乙女）じゃなくて悪魔なの！
（東条）禅さんの知り合いか？
No, he was a real Demon!
You know him?
（早乙女）知り合いじゃねえよ！
でも　知ってんだよ！→
No, I don't!
But I know about him.
いやもう細かい事はいい！
とにかく相手は人間じゃねえ→
The details don't matter!
What matters is that you
weren't fighting a human!
He was a real Demon (akuma)!
本物の悪魔だ！ア・ク・マ！
A! Ku! Ma!
わかったら
もうカラむんじゃねえぞ！
うんうん→
Understand? Then don't
tangle with them again!
Ah! Kuma (bear)?
あ！くま！か。ちゃうわ～！！
Not even close!
He was as strong as a bear, it's true.
確かにクマみたいに強かったな。
So, where can I go to fight him again?
で　どこに行けば
もう一回　戦えるんだ？
くくく…。
禅さん→
Zen-san...
オレ　もう一回聞けば
わかるような気がしてきたぜ。
I've got the feeling like I could
understand if you explained once more.
Please! Explain it to me
once again, from the start!
頼む　もう一回最初から説明してくれ。
Come with me, you!
（早乙女）
ちょっとお前　こっち来い！
こっちで話そう！
We'll talk over there!
（東条）オレ　すげぇ強えヤツと
ケンカしたんだ。→
I fought with this crazy strong guy...
でも　メチャクチャに
やられちまってよ。
But I was beat bad... Real bad.
（早乙女）そうか！
お前も災難だったな！
I guess you had it rough too!
うああああっ！！
ダアアアアッ！！
レレレレレ～！
ダダダダダ～！
《フフッ　わかる　わかるぞ！→
I get it! I get it now!
Something is trying to
awaken from inside of me!
今　オレの中で
何かが目覚めようとしている！》
おお　武の神よ！
これが　悟りというヤツですか！？
Oh, god of fighting!
Is this what they call enlightenment?
まさしく　ニューオレ様の誕生！ダッダー！
Our goal: The birth of a Great New Me!
…なワケ　ね～だろ！
アイ～。
As if!
These grounds are huge!
広いし！落ち葉無限だし！
もはや道場カンケ～ねえし～！
There's an infinite number of fallen leaves!
This doesn't have anything
to do with the dojo!
アイダダダ～！
ふざけんじゃねえぞ～！
Stop screwing with me!
No matter how deep down the stains...
コラ！じじい！！
うん？
Hey, old man!
もう　テメェぶったおして修業おわりだ～！
ガルルル…。
I'm gonna beat the crap out
of you and end this training!
Oh? Giving up already?
ほう　もう音をあげたか→
I thought you'd have more guts.
案外　根性ないのう。
うぐっ！
I want you to teach me techniques 'n stuff!
技とか　そういうのを
教えろっつってんだ！
こんなもん　雑用だろうが！何の意味あんだよ！
These are just chores!
What's the point?!
最後までやればわかる。
ま　あきらめるなら止めんがね。
You'll understand if you complete them.
I won't stop you if you want to quit though.
うっく…。
うぅ～…おもしれぇなぁ
クソじじい～。
Interesting, you old bastard.
オラァーッ！
ワチャーッ！
ちきしょ～！はっぱ一枚残さず
集めてやらぁ～！
Damn it! I'm gonna collect every last leaf!
ダダダダダー！
レレレレレー！
あん？
ダ？
フッ…。
キイイ～！
ブブブ…。
ダダダ…！
（コン！）
あっ。
ヒ…ヒ…ヒ…。
でぇっ！
ビエエエ～！
ギャア～！
またこのパターンかぁ～！！
The same joke exactly?!
フッフッフ…。
Is this it?
（黒木）ここか。かつて国盗りの門とまでうたわれた→
So this is the dojo of the Shingetsu School, once
heralded as the gateway to controlling the country.
心月流の道場は。
Wait, are we really going to do this?
（三鏡）
つ～か　ホントに行くのかよ。
当然じゃあ。みんなで
（鬼塚）
強くなるって決めたじゃろ。
Of course!
We all decided to get stronger, remember?
（出崎）そうよ～　今さら
怖気づかないでくれる？
That's right! Don't go
having second thoughts now.
Yes. Teimo Tech's Shadow Group
lives and dies together.
（黒木）ああ　われら
帝毛工業影組は一蓮托生。
（三鏡）へ～へ～
確かに石矢魔の連中には→
Yeah, sure... Definitely gotta get
revenge on those guys from Ishiyama.
リベンジしねえとな。
たのも～！
Excuse us!
誰かいませんこと～？うん？
Anyone there?
（鬼塚）そこの御仁　よろしいか？→
You there, lad! May we have a moment?
実は我々４人　こちらの道場に
入門させていただきたいのじゃが。
The four of us here would like
to join this dojo, you see...
入門？
Join?
やめとけ　一生庭そうじ
させられるだけだぞ。
Give it up. You'll just have to clean
the grounds for the rest of your lives.
（４人）んなっ！？
きさま　男鹿！
Damn you, it's Oga!
何でこんなところに！？
Why are you here?
Huh? And who might you be?
あ？どちらさん？
（黒木）お約束だな！
That's our cue!
帝毛の影組じゃあ～！
We're Teimo's Shadow Group!
If you forgot, then we'll make you remember!
忘れたなら
思い出させてあげる！
てか　これもう
やられるセリフじゃね？
Um, we just set ourselves
up to lose, didn't we?
誰だか知らんが…。
I don't know who the hell you are...
ウオッ！
せっかく！
...but you went...
...and scattered...
ぐはぁ！
集めた！
...all the leaves...
落ち葉を～！
...I gathered!
撒き散らすんじゃね～！（４人）すんませんでした～！
We're very sorry!
ウッ！
《何だ　今　まるでホウキを
自分の体の一部のように…》
What?
It was like the broom was
a part of my own body...
なんだよ　やっぱ
強くなってんじゃねえか。
What's this?
I really have gotten stronger!
Is it finally time for a Great New Me?!
ついにニューオレ様の誕生かぁ！？
（ガッ！）
ぐはっ！
As if.
んなワケあるか。
いってぇ～。
（祖父）
ったく　このバチ当たりが。→
Ow!
You've got no respect.
神聖な境内でケンカなぞしおって。
Fighting on the sacred grounds!
What? Weren't you teaching me how to
use a wooden sword with the broom?
何だよ！ホウキで木刀の使い方
教えてくれてたんじゃねえのかよ！？
If that was all it took to
learn, we'd all be masters.
そんなもんで
教えられたら苦労せんわい。
じゃあアレか！？
オレのやった事って→
Then it's that?! All that
work I did was pointless?!
やっぱ何の意味もなかったのか！？
ほれ。
（祖父）
あ？
Here.
I roasted these potatoes in the leaves.
落ち葉でイモが焼けた。
どうじゃ　意味あったろ？
See? There was a point to it.
Yeah, but...
いや…だから…その…くっ！
そ～ゆ～こっちゃ　ね～んだよぉ！
That's not what I meant!
I can't say I'm 100%, but
thanks to you, I'm doing okay.
元通りとはいかんが
おかげで落ち着いたよ。
世話をかけたな
フォルカス　ラミア。
Sorry for all the trouble, Furcas, Lamia...
ヒルダ姉さま。
またヒルダ姉さまの声が聞けて→
Miss Hilda!
I'm so glad I can hear your
voice again, Miss Hilda!
うれしいです。
本当によかった。
Thank goodness...
だが　油断はできん。
But we cannot breathe easy.
ヘカドズの槍には　悪魔の力を
拡散させる効果がある。→
Hecadoth's spear has the power
to dispel the power of Demons.
しばらく安静にすることだ。
うむ。しかし…。
You must rest for a time.
Yes, but...
（フォルカス）
ヤツらは近いうちにまた来る。→
They will come again shortly.
…が　ヤツらが次元転送に
使っていたのは　おそらく→
But the dimensional transfer they used...
国宝と呼ばれる宝具。
It's likely a Royal treasure...
となれば　もう一度転送に必要な
魔力を貯めるのにかかる時間は→
In that case, it will take time to gather
the magic power to transfer again.
About one week.
およそ一週間。
その間に　何とか対策を考えねばならん。
We must think of a plan before then.
ラミア。
はい？
Lamia.
Yes?
Will you do me a favor?
ひとつ頼まれてはくれないか。
姉さまの頼みでしたら何でも！
For you, I'll do anything!
In the week before they come,
I'd like you to find Lord En.
ヤツらが来るまでの
一週間の間に→
焔王坊っちゃまを
探し出してほしい。
エッ！？
ダアダブッダ～！
Hey! You're going to
disturb the neighborhood!
ちょっと！近所迷惑でしょ！
でやあぁ～！！
キャッ！
ダダ～！
Quiet down!
（邦枝）静かにしなさ～い！
実はこのあと…。
And after that...
（警官）な～にを考えてるんだね！
キミらは！→
What the hell are you people thinking?
奇声を発しながら
自転車で２人乗りとは！
Two on a bike, screaming
at the top of your lungs?!
（邦枝）ハァ…すみません。
ほら　男鹿もあやまんなさい。
We're sorry...
Come on, Oga, apologize!
チッ　反省してま～す。
アチャブ。
My bad.
You mustn't ride two to a bike, understand?
自転車の２人乗りは
絶対にいけませんぞ！
フハハハ…！
Here we go, Furuichi!
We have to find Lord En, and quick!
Why am I coming?
Don't get the wrong idea...
Miss Hilda can't move, Oga's off training,
so I don't have anyone else to ask, got it?
Tsundere...
Did my heart just do a little...
No way! I have zero interest
in this little bed-wetter!
On the next Beelzebub: "Where Might
My Brother Have Disappeared To?"
In the end, Hilda-san's
meaty thighs are the best!
Ickichi, you disgust me.